It's that...
m 'lady
I knew you'd return to help
trying to dream up and
see if we're right now.
I'm probably going to
have a whole lot of fun.
I'm tired of this, but I
don't think I'm afraid.
I'm tired of this,
but I don't think I'm afraid.
I won't be trying to dream up.
I won't be afraid of this,
but I won't be afraid.
I won't be afraid, but I won't be afraid.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
I have just returned
from the Eastern Gate.
There is not much time
before it crumbles away,
and the Army of the Dark marches through.
They have 50,000.
We have but 3,000.
As far as training them,
we are doing all we can.
And where are the other Integrity Knights?
Are they all out on patrol?
As I made my approach,
I could only see seven.
They are all we have here. What?
That is impossible!
Counting the two of us, there
should be 31 Knights in the Order!
Technically, there are, m 'lady.
But you know as well as I,
when a knight showed signs of distress,
Chudelkin would use the
arts to recalibrate them.
At the last count, ten knights
have yet to be awakened from that.
Currently, twenty-one knights are active.
There are four stationed at the
cathedral to guard the capital,
and four are on patrol
over the End Mountains.
That only leaves thirteen, then.
Needless to say, we are
stretched far too thin.
And with all that we face,
You brought him.
Do you intend to protect
him while you fight?
Yes, of course.
I've sworn to protect him!
But how can you?
He is nothing but dead weight.
If you burden yourself with him!
Not only will it affect
your ability to fight?
It'll place you in certain danger.
That's enough Eldrie, a relax.
Hey, little girl!
You look like you've been
taking care of yourself.
Even your cheeks filled in.
Hello, uncle!
It has been too long.
Commander!
What's wrong?
Is he going to kill Kirito?
No need for that, kid.
Uncle all right tell me what you saw i
think i saw the flash of swords just now.
I tossed an incarnate
sword at him well actually
was more like a dagger it
only would have scratched
his cheek a bit if it
hit him that is if it hit
then that means he that's
right he stopped it.
He did it with his willpower.
It might not look like
his mind's all there
but the kid ain't dead
no way and he wasn't
protecting himself when
he blocked my strike he
was protecting you he'll
snap out of it one day?
That's what I think.
I can't tell you when, but I bet
it'll be when you need him the most.
Don't get hung up on
the small stuff, Eldrie.
We can look after this kid easy.
Right.
I shall get them.
Kirito.
Even though the battle with
Administrator cost you your heart, still,
you had the will to protect me
from Uncle's sword technique.
Tell me.
What do you think of me?
And to that end, what do I think of you?
Ridiculous.
I am unnatural.
A puppet created to fight using
Alice Suberg's body as a vessel.
I am not allowed the luxury of emotions.
Only the will to do battle.
Although, what if that is why
I cannot break through to you?
Because I hold myself back.
Would you respond if I
unleashed all of my will?
Right now?
Uh, um...
We-we brought some
supper for you, m 'lady.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
Oh, and...
Here is your bread and drink.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I see by your uniforms.
You are from the Swordcraft Academy.
Yes, my lady, we are.
I'm Primary Trainee Tiese Streenan,
Army Supply Corps, at your service.
And I'm Primary Trainee
Ronie Arabelle, ma 'am.
You do not have to be so formal with me.
I am a warrior, here to
protect the land, same as you.
So please, call me Alice.
What is wrong? Huh?
No, nothing.
It's just that when we first
met you at the academy,
you seemed different than you are now.
Oh, was I?
Anyway, is there something
I can do for you?
Yes, I think.
Um, sorry to primally,
I mean, Alice,
but the word around the camp is that
you came here with a black-haired boy.
We knew someone at the academy like that,
and we thought we'd come see if
it was him, if you don't mind.
No, of course I do not mind.
Now that I recall, you were friends
of Kirito's at the academy. I knew it!
It is Kirito!
Then Yujiro must be here too! Yeah!
I am sorry.
There is no easy way to say this.
I do not wish to upset you.
However, since Yujiro and Kirito were
your mentors, you have the right to know.
Oh, my God.
Just now, I heard him.
It was you, Joe.
He said not to cry.
And he'll be here, always.
I am sorry.
You must love them dearly.
Don't say that!
We...
we could never...
Lady Alice, when you arrested Kirito
and Yuji-Oh, did you know what they did?
Yes, they violated one of the taboos.
They were involved in
the death of another.
And...
do you know what led up to
them breaking that taboo?
No, not entirely.
They raised their swords to save us.
Because we weren't strong
enough to save ourselves.
If only we'd handled
our troubles ourselves.
They wouldn't have rebelled
against the laws of the church.
And no one would have died.
Ultimately, we are the ones
to blame for what happened.
That's why, no matter how
we truly feel about them.
We can't say we love them.
It is not your fault.
You've done nothing wrong.
But we have!
You're a noble Integrity
Knight, so you can't understand!
We're sinners!
We cause bloodshed by
letting ourselves be defiled!
The body is nothing more than a vessel.
Your soul, your heart, your
soul, is who you really are.
And you determine the nature of your soul.
You and you alone.
Show them.
Just like Kirito showed you.
You see the person you
really are is but the
reflection of your heart
and that cannot be defiled.
I was born in a tiny
village I should have grown
up to become who you see
now but when I was just
a child I was arrested for
a crime my memories were
erased and I was turned
into an integrity knight
there were times I cursed
my fate however kirito
taught me to overcome
it that I had the power
to I just had to will it
and I won't doubt myself
again I've chosen to
accept who I am and move on
I am sure given time the two of you
will also find your way and find peace?
Hey.
Uncle.
Good morning.
I was thinking about your friend just now,
and what to do with him
when the fighting starts.
I have already made arrangements.
Last night, I was paid a visit by
his former pages from the Academy.
I trust them, so I asked them
to look after Kirito. Good.
Glad that's settled.
By the way, how'd the kid take it?
Did seeing these folks from
his past snap Malvis Fog any?
Mama.
Oh, well.
Chin up.
Something tells me he'll come
around, and when he does,
he'll be the one who sets
the course of this war.
Even if he got help from
you and his partner,
killing the Prime Senator and the
Pontifex was anything but easy.
If I took him on, I doubt I'd last
against his incarnate ability.
You exaggerate.
Yesterday, when our wills
clashed, I definitely felt it.
That kid's got equal, or hell, even
more experience in real combat than me.
But how is that possible?
You are much older.
Not an experience.
He's got way more.
The Taboo Index forbids
battles to the death,
but he's got tons of experience with that.
Question is, how?
Uncle, he is not from -
Commander!
It is time for the Council.
Lady Fanatio.
She's wearing... makeup?
It has been ages, Alice.
You've been well, I take it?
So feminine.
Yes, and you?
As well as can be.
Say, is it true you brought
that black-haired boy here?
I have.
Good.
After our meeting, I would
like to see him for a moment.
For what reason?
I wish to thank him.
It won't take long. Thank him? Indeed.
Even though he defeated
me, he fought honorably.
Truth be told, that boy is the only
male who fought me with all he had.
It did not matter to him in the
slightest that I happened to be a woman.
Why would that matter?
When I first became a knight and fought
with men, I could tell they held back.
So I donned this helmet and
mastered the art of continuous
attacks to prevent my opponents
from getting too close.
Ultimately, the real issue was that
I was self-conscious about my gender.
He saw right through me, though, and
fought with all his might regardless.
I unleashed all of my sword techniques
and arts, and he still bested me.
Then, after I healed, my petty
obsession had disappeared entirely.
There, now do you understand
why I am so eager to thank him?
I am also a tad vexed, to be honest.
My femininity did not register with
him at all once he saw my face.
I thought if I saw him I could try a few
things that might stimulate his recovery.
I am grateful for your concern,
but he is resting at the moment.
I will make sure to give him your
regards when I check on him later.
Oh, it seems you've installed
yourself as his guardian.
Well, whenever the commander was on
duty and you wished to speak with him.
I never refused you, not even once.
I do not need your permission.
I can see him anytime I choose.
and another thing if you
truly wish to be beaten
senseless by a male surely
uncle here could have.
obliged you i would not
expect him to he is the
strongest swordsman in the
land he would not spar.
with his knights full
bore oh you don't say well
whenever i trained with
him he was always drenched.
in sweat from the exertion.
Come on, it's time we
got this meeting started.
We have considered many
different strategies
over the past four months
and have concluded that,
at our current strength,
it would be difficult to
repel an all-out attack.
On our side of the End Mountains,
there is nothing but grassland and rocks
for ten key lords in all directions.
If the enemy advances this far, we
will be surrounded and slaughtered.
Our only option is to engage
them in this narrow ravine,
which is 100 miles wide
and 1,000 miles long.
We will set up a defensive position here,
absorb their charge, and grind them down.
This will be the basic
thrust of our strategy.
Does anyone have any thoughts so far?
I have a concern.
The enemy has ogres and longbows,
and even more dangerous,
dark mages of untold numbers.
How can we counteract
their long-range attacks?
I have an idea on that.
There is no sunlight in that
ravine, even during the day.
Not even the grass grows.
Sacred power is sparse there at best.
But in theory, if we absorb the
power from the battlefield first,
their mages won't be able
to use it to attack us.
The same is true for our side as well.
At the present, we only have
100 who can wield the arts.
If we allow the battle to come
down to our wielders and theirs,
theirs will use far more power.
The arts are not just
used for combat, though.
If all the sacred power is exhausted,
healing the lives of our critically
wounded will be next to impossible.
I admit, it is a risky gamble,
which is why we brought all the reagents
and healing potions from the capital.
If we use our sacred arts only for
healing and the potions for support,
the reagents should last
for at least three days.
There is one more issue, if I may.
While Solus and Terraria's
blessings are sparse there,
during the battle, with
each warrior who falls,
more sacred power will be
released and accumulate.
I do not see how we can
absorb all those extra
resources if there are
not enough of us to do so.
We can.
Well, actually, one of us can.
Who?
Why you, Alice Synthesis 30.
Perhaps you haven't realized it yet,
but your power has surpassed that of
all the Integrity Knights in the land,
and you are ready to use it now.
A godlike power that can
split heaven and earth.
Would you please look after
Kirito and keep him safe?
Yes, you can count on us.
Lady Alice, don't you worry.
We promise we will protect
him with our lives.
Kirito, I must leave, and I
do not know if I shall return.
You saved my life, and I will use all of
it, to the last drop if I have to. And so,
should I fall in battle and call
you with the last of my breath,
would you stand and
draw your sword for me?
With you awake, it would not matter
how many thousands the enemy has.
You will perform another miracle
and protect everyone, as before.
After all, you were the one
who defeated the Administrator.
You are the greatest swordsman ever.
Lady Alice.
Are you ready to go?
Eldrie? Yes?
Milady?
Thank you.
You have served me well.
I was blessed to have you by my side,
even though it was not for long.
You chose an amateur like
me to be your mentor,
instead of a male veteran
like Serdeo Selbert.
Was that out of sympathy for me?
No, not at all!
I would never be so disrespectful!
I chose you because I was so in awe of your
sword technique and skills as a warrior.
And it is due to your unwavering support
that I was able to survive to see this day.
I thank you.
Lady Alice, you speak with such finality.
It is as if you think your journey,
instead of going on, is about to end.
It cannot!
I still have not learned
all I can from you!
My technique, my arts,
I am nowhere near ready.
I still need you to continue my training
and guide me to be a better knight.
Integrity Knight, Eldrie Synthesis 31.
Yes, m 'lady.
As your mentor, here are my final orders.
You will survive.
Survive to witness peace in the land.
And after, you will seek out your true life
and take it back, and the one you love.
That's it.
Yeah!
I